<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>System Information on</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/</link><description>Recent content in System Information on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guide Overview</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/guide_overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/guide_overview/</guid><description>This user guide contains set up, operation, and other information about the NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System. It is for 1.4 system models or systems upgraded to software version 1.4.
General Information #
Manufacturer:
Alcon Laboratories, Inc.
6201 South Freeway
Fort Worth, TX 76134-2099, USA
Made in the USA with global materials
Produced By:
Alcon Research, LLC.
15800 Alcon Parkway
Irvine, CA 92618-3818, USA
Alcon Laboratories Belgium
Lichterveld 3
2870 Puurs-Sint-Amands</description></item><item><title>System Overview</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/system_overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/system_overview/</guid><description>System Description #
The Alcon NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is a 3D stereoscopic, high-definition digital video camera and workstation that operates as an adjunct to a surgical microscope during surgery. The system displays real-time images or images from recordings on a flat-panel, high-definition digital 3D display device, positioned for viewing video. There is no additional light (or energy) delivered by the system.
Intended Use #
The NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is intended to aid trained surgeons in visualization during ophthalmic surgery.</description></item><item><title>Limited Warranty</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/warranty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/warranty/</guid><description>Alcon Laboratories, Inc., will repair or replace at its option, any system or accompanying accessories found to be defective in material and/or workmanship for a period of one (1) year from the date of initial installation. This warranty applies to the original purchaser of the system, when said system is properly installed, maintained, and operated in accordance with published instructions.
Alcon Laboratories shall not be obligated to provide services under this warranty for damage to or destruction of systems covered where such damage or destruction is (i) a result of or caused by fire or explosion of any origin, riot, civil commotion, aircraft, war, or any Act of God including, but not limited to lightning, windstorm, hail, flood, earthquake, or (ii) caused by customer’s misuse or improper servicing of said systems.</description></item><item><title>System Components</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/components/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/components/</guid><description>At a minimum, the system includes the cart, camera, microscope, 3D glasses, keyboard, and touchpad. To optimize operation, incorporate additional devices such as the following:
1 System &amp;ndash; Receives video from the camera and displays 3D images. 2 Patient Bed &amp;ndash; Holds the patient at a comfortable level. 3 Microscope stand &amp;ndash; Suspends a microscope above the patient. 4 Camera &amp;ndash; Captures 3D video. 5 Microscope &amp;ndash; Magnifies the view of the camera.</description></item><item><title>Specifications</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/specifications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/specifications/</guid><description>General Specifications #
Topic Value Weight (unpacked) 133 kg (294 lb) Weight (packed) 333 kg (734 lb) Dimensions (unpacked) 82.6 cm L x 122.7 cm W x 193.8 cm H (32.5” L x 48.3” W x 76.3” H) Dimensions (packed) 106.7 cm L x 153.2 cm W x 177.3 cm H (42” L x 60.3” W x 69.8” H) Environmental Specifications #
Topic Value Temperature (operating) 5 °C to 30 °C (41 °F to 86 °F) Temperature (storage and transport) 0 °C to 50 °C (32 °F to 122 °F) Relative humidity (operating) 15% to 85% non-condensing Relative humidty (storage and transport) 10% to 90% non-condensing Atmospheric pressure 100 to 75 kPa Atmospheric pressure 100 to 30 kPa</description></item></channel></rss>