<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System on</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/</link><description>Recent content in NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Say hello to Doks 👋</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/blog/say-hello-to-doks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/blog/say-hello-to-doks/</guid><description>Introducing Doks, a Hugo theme helping you build modern documentation websites that are secure, fast, and SEO-ready — by default.</description></item><item><title>Guide Overview</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/guide_overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/guide_overview/</guid><description>This user guide contains set up, operation, and other information about the NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System. It is for 1.4 system models or systems upgraded to software version 1.4.
General Information Manufacturer:
Alcon Laboratories, Inc.
6201 South Freeway
Fort Worth, TX 76134-2099, USA
Made in the USA with global materials
Produced By:
Alcon Research, LLC.
15800 Alcon Parkway
Irvine, CA 92618-3818, USA
Alcon Laboratories Belgium
Lichterveld 3
2870 Puurs-Sint-Amands
Belgium</description></item><item><title>System Overview</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/system_overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/system_overview/</guid><description>System Description The Alcon NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is a 3D stereoscopic, high-definition digital video camera and workstation that operates as an adjunct to a surgical microscope during surgery. The system displays real-time images or images from recordings on a flat-panel, high-definition digital 3D display device, positioned for viewing video. There is no additional light (or energy) delivered by the system.
Intended Use The NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System is intended to aid trained surgeons in visualization during ophthalmic surgery.</description></item><item><title>General Safety Information</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_safety/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_safety/</guid><description>In addition to reading this user guide, all users must be trained by an Alcon employee or a trainer that has been designated by Alcon. The trainee must be comfortable working as an interface between the doctor and the NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System, and the trainee must be familiar with pre-operative room and operating room protocols.
For customers in the U.S.A.
Federal Law restricts this device to sale by or on the order of a licensed medical practitioner.</description></item><item><title>General Warnings and Precautions</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_warnings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_warnings/</guid><description>Pay close attention to warnings and cautions. A warning statement is written to protect individuals from bodily harm. A caution statement is written to protect the instrument from damage. This section is for general system warnings and precautions only.
WARNING In case of a deficiency, do not use the system; call Alcon Technical Services. Use of accessories other than those provided may affect system performance and create potential hazards. If it is determined that an accessory not provided by Alcon has contributed to the malfunction of the equipment during the warranty period, service will be provided at prevailing hourly rates.</description></item><item><title>EMC Compliance</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/emc_compliance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/emc_compliance/</guid><description>The NGENUITY™ system is designed to work in the Professional Healthcare facility environment.
The NGENUITY™ system requires special precautions regarding EMC and needs to be installed and put into service according to the EMC information provided in the below tables.
The NGENUITY™ system is a medical device designated for Indoor Use Only.
WARNING Use of this system adjacent to or stacked with other equipment should be avoided because it could result in improper operation.</description></item><item><title>Wireless Certification and Compliance Information</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/wireless/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/wireless/</guid><description>Cart (Communication Link with Centurion) Frequency or frequency band of transmission: 2.405 GHz to 2.480 GHz Type and frequency characteristics of the modulation: OQPSK (offset quadrature phase-shift keying) Effective Radiated Power (ERP): 11.3 dBm (13.40 mW) USA - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) This device complies with part 15 of the FCC Rules. Operation is subject to the following two conditions: (1) This device may not cause harmful interference, and (2) this device must accept any interference received, including interference that may cause undesired operation.</description></item><item><title>Label Locations</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/label_locations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/label_locations/</guid><description>Note the safety and system label locations. Refer to the system for specific information.
1 Moving parts warning label &amp;ndash; Includes a warning related to a protective guard. 2 Identifies compatible connectors. &amp;ndash; The location and connector type varies with the display model. 3 Oculars storage warning label &amp;ndash; Includes information about storing the microscope oculars. 4 Product label &amp;ndash; Includes information about the system. 5 Wireless label &amp;ndash; Indicates wireless capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Serious Incident Reporting</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/serious_incidents/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/serious_incidents/</guid><description>Any serious incident related to the use of this medical device should be reported to Alcon Laboratories, Inc.
By phone: In USA – (800) 757-9780
In EU/International – Contact the local country office or your Alcon distributor.
By website: http://www.alcon.com/contact-us/
By email: qa.complaints@alcon.com
These serious incidents should also be reported to the competent authority for medical devices of your Member State.</description></item><item><title>Limited Warranty</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/warranty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/warranty/</guid><description>Alcon Laboratories, Inc., will repair or replace at its option, any system or accompanying accessories found to be defective in material and/or workmanship for a period of one (1) year from the date of initial installation. This warranty applies to the original purchaser of the system, when said system is properly installed, maintained, and operated in accordance with published instructions.
Alcon Laboratories shall not be obligated to provide services under this warranty for damage to or destruction of systems covered where such damage or destruction is (i) a result of or caused by fire or explosion of any origin, riot, civil commotion, aircraft, war, or any Act of God including, but not limited to lightning, windstorm, hail, flood, earthquake, or (ii) caused by customer’s misuse or improper servicing of said systems.</description></item></channel></rss>