<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Settings on</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/</link><description>Recent content in Settings on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Settings Menu</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/settings_menu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/settings_menu/</guid><description>To adjust image settings, click Settings.
1 Vit System button &amp;ndash; Includes overlay options and imaging mode linking. 2 Phaco System button &amp;ndash; Includes overlay options. 3 Screen Layout button &amp;ndash; Adjusts the display layout and what features are included during surgical cases. 4 Recording button &amp;ndash; Sets video parameters. 5 Color Channels button &amp;ndash; Manages color emphasis. 6 Light Profiles button &amp;ndash; Adjusts colors depending on the light source. 7 Imaging Modes button &amp;ndash; Manages imaging modes.</description></item><item><title>Constellation™ Settings</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/constellation_settings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/constellation_settings/</guid><description>To access the Constellation™ Overlay options, click Constellation™.
1 Opacity slider &amp;ndash; Lower the slider to make the overlay text more transparent or raise the slider to make the overlay text less transparent. 2 Show on-screen toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enables Constellation™ data to show on the display. 3 Imaging Mode Linking toggle switch &amp;ndash; Automatically switches system imaging modes when a Constellation™ surgical step is changed. The default imaging modes are used for linking and are created if they do not already exist.</description></item><item><title>Centurion™ Settings</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/centurion_settings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/centurion_settings/</guid><description>To access the Centurion™ Overlay options, click Centurion™.
1 Opacity slider &amp;ndash; Lower the slider to make the overlay text more transparent or raise the slider to make the overlay text less transparent. 2 Enlarge Overlay toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enlarges the overlay features. 3 Show Only in Recording toggle switch &amp;ndash; Hides Centurion™ overlay information during operation, but displays it in recordings. NOTE: If the Centurion™ overlay is displayed on-screen, enable the record DataFusion toggle in Recording settings to capture the overlays in recorded video files.</description></item><item><title>Screen Layout</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/screen_layout/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/screen_layout/</guid><description>To access the Screen Layout options, click Screen Layout. To set basic layout features, click Basic. To set advanced layout features, click Advanced.
1 Patient Info drop-down menu &amp;ndash; Sets the frequency in which patient information displays during operation. 2 PiP Location &amp;ndash; Sets the screen corner to display input from the secondary source during PiP layout. This option applies only when Secondary Viewport is set to PiP. 3 Secondary Viewport buttons &amp;ndash; Sets the layout for a secondary viewport the Screen Layout button switches to when clicked.</description></item><item><title>Recording Settings</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/recording_settings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/recording_settings/</guid><description>To access Recording options, click Recording.
NOTICE Recording settings cannot be changed while recording video. Basic and Advanced #
To set basic settings, click Basic. To set advanced settings, click Advanced.
1 Movies Format buttons &amp;ndash; Saves video files as .avi or .mov files. 2 Show Logo toggle switch &amp;ndash; Displays the system logo in the bottom-left corner during operation if Record DataFusion is disabled. 3 Auto-Record toggle switch &amp;ndash; Automatically starts recording when a case starts.</description></item><item><title>Color Channel Management</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/color_channels/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/color_channels/</guid><description>To access Color Channel options, click Color Channel. The system previews adjusted color channels in the Color Channel dialog box.
Editing Color Channels #
Click an existing color channel. Click Edit. In the Name field, enter a new name if needed. Adjust the sliders to place emphasis on certain colors. Enable Advanced Settings to adjust brightness, contrast, gamma correction, hue, and saturation. Adding Color Channels #
Click Add. In the Name field, enter a descriptive name.</description></item><item><title>Light Profile Settings</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/light_profiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/light_profiles/</guid><description>Light profile settings correct color for different illumination sources. To access Light Profile options, click Light Profile. Alcon recommends matching the illumination source with the corresponding light profile.
1 Light Source selection &amp;ndash; Sets the applicable light source type. 2 White Balance button &amp;ndash; Sets white balance for the selected light source. Follow the on-screen instructions to complete the process. White balance optimizes image quality. Perform this process when the microscope or endo-illumination settings change, the lamps change, or the image quality or color balances are not optimized.</description></item><item><title>Imaging Mode Management</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/imaging_mode/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/imaging_mode/</guid><description>Imaging modes are a core visualization baseline for routine cases. To access Imaging Mode options, click Imaging Mode. If operating with different illumination sources or optical systems that require inverted camera orientation, Alcon recommends creating a custom imaging mode to accommodate individual surgical workflows.
The default imaging modes include the following:
Imaging Mode Camera Orientation Light Profile Anterior Standard Halogen Posterior Inverted Constellation™ Macular Standard Constellation™ To copy, edit, or delete imaging modes, click Unlock and then Confirm.</description></item><item><title>Language</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/language/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/language/</guid><description>The Language system settings control the language the system displays. Contact Technical Services for additional languages.
To change the language, perform the following:
In the Language drop-down menu, select a language. Click Confirm.</description></item><item><title>System Settings</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/system_settings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/settings/system_settings/</guid><description>System settings apply to all doctor profiles on the system and are primarily related to connecting devices to the system. They also include system information. To access System Setting options, click System Settings.
DataFusion #
The DataFusion settings determine which device is connected to the system. To access DataFusion options, click DataFusion. The system can only enable one device at a time.
1 Constellation™ toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enables Constellation™ connection. 2 Centurion™ toggle switch &amp;ndash; Enables Centurion™ connection.</description></item></channel></rss>