<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>System Setup on</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/</link><description>Recent content in System Setup on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Startup Procedure</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/startup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/startup/</guid><description>WARNING System isolation from mains is achieved through detachment of power cord. Turn OFF the power switch and unplug the power cord from wall outlet to achieve isolation from mains. Do not bypass the isolation transformer and connect any of the NGENUITY™ components directly to a wall outlet. To avoid risk of electric shock, this equipment must only be connected to a supply mains with protective earth (ground). The system should be connected to an uninterruptible power source when loss of power would result in an unacceptable risk.</description></item><item><title>System Position and Articulation</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/positioning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/positioning/</guid><description>Before operating the system, position the system and all components for optimal user conditions.
System Movement #
CAUTION Do not push or pull unit by the display or any cable. The unit should be pulled and not pushed, especially over elevator and door thresholds. To move the system around the room, unlock the casters. Each castor on the cart has three modes, controlled by the brake pedal. Set each castor in total lock mode while the system is being used.</description></item><item><title>Camera Configuration</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/camera_config/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/camera_config/</guid><description>Camera Sensor Initialization #
Sensor initialization helps prevent image degradation and noise. Perform the following steps during startup or after camera connection. A message to expose the camera to more light appears.
NOTE Image quality is also influenced by other factors. Turn on all room lights.
Open the camera iris to 100%.
Position the white balance card at 90 degrees under the microscope objective lens. The message disappears within 5 seconds.</description></item><item><title>White Balance</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/white_balance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/white_balance/</guid><description>To calibrate light settings, verify the light temperature and perform the white balance procedure. Before setting white balance, perform the following checks:
Set the camera iris slider to normal working conditions for the user. Alcon recommends 30%. Set the microscope to maximum zoom. Disable any red reflex settings. Remove all extraneous devices (for example, beam splitters or invertors). Disable any unique microscope filtration or lens settings (for example, laser filters). Ensure the microscope is not tiled.</description></item><item><title>Setup Recommendations</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/recommendations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/setup/recommendations/</guid><description>To extend the depth of field and improve performance at high magnification, follow these tips:
Parfocalize visualization (microscope, non-contact, contact) to focus the surgical space. Zoom in to fill the display to maximize the quality of surgical view.</description></item></channel></rss>