<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Service and Maintenance on</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/</link><description>Recent content in Service and Maintenance on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shutdown Procedure</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/shutdown/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/shutdown/</guid><description> On the Home screen, click Power. Click Shut Down. Wait for the EPU indicators next to the USB connectors (see Cart) to turn off (~30 s). Turn off the power switch at the base of the cart.</description></item><item><title>Cleaning</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/cleaning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/cleaning/</guid><description>Clean the system by periodically wiping down with a dry, lint-free cloth. Use warm water and mild detergent on non-electrical system components (for example, the cart, exterior cart panels, and 3D glasses). Wipe down the camera and camera cable with isopropyl alcohol. Wipe the display with a soft, dry cloth. Use less than 0.10 lb. of force on the display. Water-based cleaners may damage the coating on the screen. WARNING Only factory-authorized personnel should service the system or system components.</description></item><item><title>Storage and Transportation</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/storage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/storage/</guid><description>To store or transport the system within the facility, perform the following:
Route the camera cable.
a. Disconnect the camera cable from the camera.
b. Wrap camera cable around the camera cable coil. Route the power cable.
a. Disconnect the power cable from the outlet.
b. Wrap power cable around the power cable coil. If the system includes a connected DataFusion device, disconnect the cable on the other device.</description></item><item><title>Alcon Service</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/service/</guid><description>For product service, please contact Alcon’s Technical Services Department at the number provided below. Operators experiencing problems with the system should refer to the Operating Instructions and Troubleshooting sections of this manual. A problem which persists should be referred to the Alcon Technical Services Department or your local authorized service representative.
For optimum performance, it is the user’s responsibility to schedule preventive maintenance service on the system and its accessories a minimum of one time per year.</description></item><item><title>Basic Maintenance</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/basic_maintenance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/basic_maintenance/</guid><description>Only factory-authorized personnel should service the system or system components.
WARNING Dangerously high voltages are present inside the components of the system. Do not open the cabinets of any system components. Refer servicing to qualified personnel only. Only authorized personnel should service the system or system components. CAUTION When removing the camera from the microscope, place it on a flat, secure area. Store the camera in the anti-static bag with the iris slider closed when it is not in use.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/docs/maintenance/troubleshooting/</guid><description>If the system exhibits the following symptoms, attempt the corresponding troubleshooting procedures before contacting Technical Services.
The image is blurry or out of focus. #
Use the microscope controls to focus the image on-screen. Check to see that the camera is flush on the microscope. Wearing the 3D glasses, close one eye at a time to check the right and left eye focus for the camera. Change the camera orientation and note if the issue remains in the same location.</description></item></channel></rss>