<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Safety Information on</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/</link><description>Recent content in Safety Information on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>General Safety Information</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_safety/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_safety/</guid><description>In addition to reading this user guide, all users must be trained by an Alcon employee or a trainer that has been designated by Alcon. The trainee must be comfortable working as an interface between the doctor and the NGENUITY™ 3D Visualization System, and the trainee must be familiar with pre-operative room and operating room protocols.
For customers in the U.S.A.
Federal Law restricts this device to sale by or on the order of a licensed medical practitioner.</description></item><item><title>General Warnings and Precautions</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_warnings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/general_warnings/</guid><description>Pay close attention to warnings and cautions. A warning statement is written to protect individuals from bodily harm. A caution statement is written to protect the instrument from damage. This section is for general system warnings and precautions only.
WARNING In case of a deficiency, do not use the system; call Alcon Technical Services. Use of accessories other than those provided may affect system performance and create potential hazards. If it is determined that an accessory not provided by Alcon has contributed to the malfunction of the equipment during the warranty period, service will be provided at prevailing hourly rates.</description></item><item><title>EMC Compliance</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/emc_compliance/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/emc_compliance/</guid><description>The NGENUITY™ system is designed to work in the Professional Healthcare facility environment.
The NGENUITY™ system requires special precautions regarding EMC and needs to be installed and put into service according to the EMC information provided in the below tables.
The NGENUITY™ system is a medical device designated for Indoor Use Only.
WARNING Use of this system adjacent to or stacked with other equipment should be avoided because it could result in improper operation.</description></item><item><title>Wireless Certification and Compliance Information</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/wireless/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/wireless/</guid><description>Cart (Communication Link with Centurion) Frequency or frequency band of transmission: 2.405 GHz to 2.480 GHz Type and frequency characteristics of the modulation: OQPSK (offset quadrature phase-shift keying) Effective Radiated Power (ERP): 11.3 dBm (13.40 mW) USA - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) This device complies with part 15 of the FCC Rules. Operation is subject to the following two conditions: (1) This device may not cause harmful interference, and (2) this device must accept any interference received, including interference that may cause undesired operation.</description></item><item><title>Label Locations</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/label_locations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/label_locations/</guid><description>Note the safety and system label locations. Refer to the system for specific information.
1 Moving parts warning label &amp;ndash; Includes a warning related to a protective guard. 2 Identifies compatible connectors. &amp;ndash; The location and connector type varies with the display model. 3 Oculars storage warning label &amp;ndash; Includes information about storing the microscope oculars. 4 Product label &amp;ndash; Includes information about the system. 5 Wireless label &amp;ndash; Indicates wireless capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Serious Incident Reporting</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/serious_incidents/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/system_information/safety/serious_incidents/</guid><description>Any serious incident related to the use of this medical device should be reported to Alcon Laboratories, Inc.
By phone: In USA – (800) 757-9780
In EU/International – Contact the local country office or your Alcon distributor.
By website: http://www.alcon.com/contact-us/
By email: qa.complaints@alcon.com
These serious incidents should also be reported to the competent authority for medical devices of your Member State.</description></item></channel></rss>