<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Operation on</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/</link><description>Recent content in Operation on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Software Overview</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/software_overview/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/software_overview/</guid><description>To navigate the system interface, use the touchpad and keyboard to select items or enter text. To start operating, select a doctor profile and patient profile.
Navigation Icons The following icons appear throughout the interface.
Icon Description Indicates the touchpad cursor location. Saves the pending changes and closes the dialog box. Switching to a different setting panel saves any pending changes. Closes the dialog box and does not save pending changes.</description></item><item><title>Doctor Profile Management</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/doctor_profiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/doctor_profiles/</guid><description>Doctor profiles save customized user settings for optimal visualization. Manage the profiles on the system from the Home panel.
1 Doctor Defaults button &amp;ndash; Saves current doctor settings as the default values or restores doctor settings to the saved default settings. 2 Doctor Export button &amp;ndash; Exports the current doctor profile to a connected USB drive. This button is only available when an external USB drive is connected. 3 Add Doctor button &amp;ndash; Creates a new doctor profile.</description></item><item><title>Patient Profile Management</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/patient_profiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/patient_profiles/</guid><description>Patient profiles store basic patient information. Manage patient profiles in the Home panel.
1 Add Patient button &amp;ndash; Creates a new patient profile. 2 Delete Patient button &amp;ndash; Deletes the selected patient profile. 3 Patient Selection drop-down menu &amp;ndash; Sets settings and patient information according to the selected patient profile. Add a Patient Profile In the Home panel, select the patient Add button. The Patient Information dialog box opens. Enter a first and last name.</description></item><item><title>Cases</title><link>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/cases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/Naem-J/web-doc-sample/docs/operation/cases/</guid><description>Live Cases In the Home panel, click Start Case.
WARNING Do not connect or disconnect any displays to the system during live surgery. Visualization is interrupted while the system reinitializes the display. Procedure Screen Layout 1 Case timer &amp;ndash; Displays the duration of the surgical case. 2 Record video button &amp;ndash; Starts and stops recording video of the screen. A red dot appears next to the case when a case is being recorded.</description></item></channel></rss>